[Music]
mental and emotional health is
foundational to our five dimensions of
health which also include physical
social spiritual and financial health
what we find that sets us apart is the
tri-fold way that we look at this
through the individual employee the
organization / supervisor and also
through the community lens our role as a
global health organization is to really
be consultative to the business to give
them measurements on how they're doing
from supporting mental and emotional
health within the workplace as well as
being consultative and advising them as
issues come up we know that our
supervisors are the key to creating
environments where there's no stigma and
we do lots of training to help them with
this an example was an event at which
three senior leaders talked about their
own experiences living with depression
addiction and post-traumatic stress
disorder these kinds of events help
employees to know that when they have
their own power challenges they come
forward and get the help they need what
we find in our day-to-day operations is
that we've built that level of trust
that we get managers HR professionals
reaching out to us for advisement and
that way we know we have hit the mark in
supporting the business
[Music]
you